VLADI FELDMAN

Frond-End Developer

- Wladi-feldman
- ✓ Vladi.fel@gmail.com
- 0547691227
- Nahalat Yetzhak 18, Tel-Aviv
- in <u>vladif</u>

SKILLS

- Front-End development using JavaScript,
 TypeScript, React, Redux,
 jQuery, HTML & CSS,
- Unit & Functional tests using Jest & Enzyme
- UX/UI design, Material-UI
- E2E Automation, Testing Methodologies.
- Perforce, Git, JIRA, Agile

EDUCATION

Tel-Aviv University, 2008-2011

B.Sc. Geophysics & Geography

Tel-Aviv University, 2012-2018

M.Sc. Geophysics

LANGUEGES

English – Highly Proficient Hebrew – Native Speaker Russian – Native Speaker

PROFILE

Meticulous and highly motivated front-end developer with 2+ years of experience in building web apps. Proficient with **JavaScript**, **Typescript**, **React**, **Redux**, **CSS**, **HTML**.

Quick learner and great team player, with high attention to details and passion for **UX/UI**, looking for a new challenge.

EXPERIENCE

Emerson (Paradigm)

Mar 2012 - Dec 2020

Enterprise technology company specializing in software solutions for the oil & gas industry.

Front-end Developer, Aug 2018 - Nov 2020

- Working as part of a Next-Gen group developing a hybrid desktop & web application that handles workflow building and large-scale mathematical operations.
- Working in close collaboration with product and design teams on new feature development from user-story to a complete working component.
- Converting UX/UI mockups into fully-functioning React components.
- Extensive work with Material-UI components and style guidlines
- o Working in Agile/ Scrum development cycles
- CI/CD working methodologies

• Automation Developer, Mar 2015 - Aug 2018

- Development & Maintenance of E2E automation tests on Windows & Linux using Squish, Python & Gherkin.
- Experience as a Scrum-master

• QA Applications Geoscientist, Mar 2012 - Mar 2015

- Science driven manual software testing
- Creation & maintenance of STD/STP/STR documents & protocols.

References will be given upon request